(function(e){function t(t){for(var a,s,o=t[0],c=t[1],u=t[2],d=0,h=[];d<o.length;d++)s=o[d],Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(r,s)&&r[s]&&h.push(r[s][0]),r[s]=0;for(a in c)Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(c,a)&&(e[a]=c[a]);l&&l(t);while(h.length)h.shift()();return i.push.apply(i,u||[]),n()}function n(){for(var e,t=0;t<i.length;t++){for(var n=i[t],a=!0,o=1;o<n.length;o++){var c=n[o];0!==r[c]&&(a=!1)}a&&(i.splice(t--,1),e=s(s.s=n[0]))}return e}var a={},r={app:0},i=[];function s(t){if(a[t])return a[t].exports;var n=a[t]={i:t,l:!1,exports:{}};return e[t].call(n.exports,n,n.exports,s),n.l=!0,n.exports}s.m=e,s.c=a,s.d=function(e,t,n){s.o(e,t)||Object.defineProperty(e,t,{enumerable:!0,get:n})},s.r=function(e){"undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.toStringTag&&Object.defineProperty(e,Symbol.toStringTag,{value:"Module"}),Object.defineProperty(e,"__esModule",{value:!0})},s.t=function(e,t){if(1&t&&(e=s(e)),8&t)return e;if(4&t&&"object"===typeof e&&e&&e.__esModule)return e;var n=Object.create(null);if(s.r(n),Object.defineProperty(n,"default",{enumerable:!0,value:e}),2&t&&"string"!=typeof e)for(var a in e)s.d(n,a,function(t){return e[t]}.bind(null,a));return n},s.n=function(e){var t=e&&e.__esModule?function(){return e["default"]}:function(){return e};return s.d(t,"a",t),t},s.o=function(e,t){return Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)},s.p="/";var o=window["webpackJsonp"]=window["webpackJsonp"]||[],c=o.push.bind(o);o.push=t,o=o.slice();for(var u=0;u<o.length;u++)t(o[u]);var l=c;i.push([0,"chunk-vendors"]),n()})({0:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n("56d7")},"2fb8":function(e,t,n){},"56d7":function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);n("e260"),n("e6cf"),n("cca6"),n("a79d");var a=n("2b0e"),r=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,n=e._self._c||t;return n("div",{attrs:{id:"app"}},[n("h1",{attrs:{id:"logo"}},[n("b-icon-lightning-fill",{attrs:{id:"lightning-bolt"}}),e._v("Flash Study "),n("b-icon-book")],1),n("b-navbar",[n("b-navbar-nav",{staticClass:"mx-auto"},e._l(e.links,(function(t){return n("li",{key:t},[n("router-link",{attrs:{to:{name:t},exact:""}},[e._v(" "+e._s(t)+" "),"create"==t?n("span",[n("b-icon-plus-circle")],1):"home"==t?n("span",[n("b-icon-house")],1):e._e()])],1)})),0)],1),n("br"),n("router-view")],1)},i=[],s={name:"App",components:{},data:function(){return{links:["home","create","newpage"]}}},o=s,c=(n("5c0b"),n("2877")),u=Object(c["a"])(o,r,i,!1,null,null,null),l=u.exports,d=n("8c4f"),h=n("5f5b"),f=n("b1e0"),g=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,n=e._self._c||t;return n("div",{attrs:{id:"categories"}},[n("h2",[e._v("Welcome to Flash Study")]),n("p",[e._v("Select a category below to get started!")]),n("b-container",e._l(e.rowCount,(function(t){return n("div",{key:t},[n("b-row",e._l(e.numberOfColumns,(function(a){return n("b-col",{key:a+e.categoriesLength+t*e.numberOfColumns},[e.categoriesLength>=e.layoutCount(t,a)?n("div",[n("show-category",{attrs:{category:Object.values(e.categories)[e.layoutCount(t,a)-1],imageWidth:e.imageWidth}})],1):e._e()])})),1)],1)})),0)],1)},m=[],p=(n("07ac"),function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,n=e._self._c||t;return n("router-link",{attrs:{to:{name:"category",params:{slug:e.category.slug}}}},[n("b-card",{staticClass:"mb-2",staticStyle:{"max-width":"40rem"},attrs:{title:e.category.name,"img-src":e.imgSource,"img-alt":"Image","img-top":""}},[n("b-card-text",[e._v("Level: "+e._s(e.category.difficulty))])],1)],1)}),w=[],b={props:["category","imageWidth"],data:function(){return{}},computed:{imgSource:function(){return"https://picsum.photos/seed/"+this.category.slug+"/"+this.imageWidth[0]+"/"+this.imageWidth[1]}}},y=b,v=Object(c["a"])(y,p,w,!1,null,"a7de6920",null),q=v.exports,C=(n("7db0"),n("4160"),n("159b"),n("96cf"),n("1da1")),x=n("d4ec"),_=n("bee2"),k=n("59ca"),A=(n("e71f"),function(){function e(t){Object(x["a"])(this,e),k["initializeApp"]({apiKey:t.apiKey,authDomain:t.projectId+".firebaseapp.com",databaseURL:"https://"+t.projectId+".firebaseio.com",projectId:t.projectId}),this.api=k["firestore"]()}return Object(_["a"])(e,[{key:"find",value:function(){var e=Object(C["a"])(regeneratorRuntime.mark((function e(t,n,a){var r;return regeneratorRuntime.wrap((function(e){while(1)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return e.prev=0,e.next=3,this.api.collection(t).where(n,"==",a).get();case 3:return r=e.sent,e.abrupt("return",r.docs.shift().data());case 7:return e.prev=7,e.t0=e["catch"](0),e.abrupt("return","Error getting documents: "+e.t0);case 10:case"end":return e.stop()}}),e,this,[[0,7]])})));function t(t,n,a){return e.apply(this,arguments)}return t}()},{key:"findID",value:function(){var e=Object(C["a"])(regeneratorRuntime.mark((function e(t,n,a){var r;return regeneratorRuntime.wrap((function(e){while(1)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return e.prev=0,e.next=3,this.api.collection(t).where(n,"==",a).get();case 3:return r=e.sent,e.abrupt("return",r.docs.id);case 7:return e.prev=7,e.t0=e["catch"](0),e.abrupt("return","Error getting documents: "+e.t0);case 10:case"end":return e.stop()}}),e,this,[[0,7]])})));function t(t,n,a){return e.apply(this,arguments)}return t}()},{key:"get",value:function(e,t){return this.find(e,"id",t)}},{key:"get_slug",value:function(e,t){return this.find(e,"slug",t)}},{key:"get_name",value:function(e,t){return this.findID(e,"name",t)}},{key:"addCard",value:function(){var e=Object(C["a"])(regeneratorRuntime.mark((function e(t,n,a){return regeneratorRuntime.wrap((function(e){while(1)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return e.prev=0,e.next=3,this.api.collection(t).doc(n).update({cards:k["firestore"].FieldValue.arrayUnion(a)});case 3:e.next=8;break;case 5:return e.prev=5,e.t0=e["catch"](0),e.abrupt("return","Error adding document: "+e.t0);case 8:case"end":return e.stop()}}),e,this,[[0,5]])})));function t(t,n,a){return e.apply(this,arguments)}return t}()},{key:"get_id_name",value:function(){var e=Object(C["a"])(regeneratorRuntime.mark((function e(t,n,a){var r;return regeneratorRuntime.wrap((function(e){while(1)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return e.prev=0,r={},e.next=4,this.api.collection(t).where(n,"==",a).get().then((function(e){e.forEach((function(e){r[e.id]=e.id}))}));case 4:return e.abrupt("return",r);case 7:e.prev=7,e.t0=e["catch"](0),console.log("Error getting documents: ",e.t0);case 10:case"end":return e.stop()}}),e,this,[[0,7]])})));function t(t,n,a){return e.apply(this,arguments)}return t}()},{key:"all",value:function(){var e=Object(C["a"])(regeneratorRuntime.mark((function e(t){var n,a;return regeneratorRuntime.wrap((function(e){while(1)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return n={},e.next=3,this.api.collection(t).get();case 3:return a=e.sent,a.forEach((function(e){n[e.id]=e.data()})),e.abrupt("return",n);case 6:case"end":return e.stop()}}),e,this)})));function t(t){return e.apply(this,arguments)}return t}()},{key:"add",value:function(){var e=Object(C["a"])(regeneratorRuntime.mark((function e(t,n){var a;return regeneratorRuntime.wrap((function(e){while(1)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return e.prev=0,e.next=3,this.api.collection(t).add(n);case 3:return a=e.sent,e.abrupt("return",a.id);case 7:return e.prev=7,e.t0=e["catch"](0),e.abrupt("return","Error adding document: "+e.t0);case 10:case"end":return e.stop()}}),e,this,[[0,7]])})));function t(t,n){return e.apply(this,arguments)}return t}()},{key:"delete",value:function(e,t){this.api.collection(e).doc(t).delete()}}]),e}()),S={firebase:{apiKey:"AIzaSyDcgSvfP2QwKCu-wHdHbHzN2ovF5z3XXZM",projectId:"e28-p2-jg"}},E=new A({apiKey:S.firebase.apiKey,projectId:S.firebase.projectId}),T={components:{"show-category":q},data:function(){return{categories:[],numberOfColumns:3,imageWidth:[200,100]}},mounted:function(){var e=this;E.all("categories").then((function(t){e.categories=t}))},computed:{rowCount:function(){return Math.floor((Object.values(this.categories).length-1)/this.numberOfColumns)+1},categoriesLength:function(){return Object.values(this.categories).length}},methods:{layoutCount:function(e,t){return(e-1)*this.numberOfColumns+t}}},j=T,I=Object(c["a"])(j,g,m,!1,null,"1e9d0940",null),O=I.exports,M=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,n=e._self._c||t;return n("b-row",{staticClass:"justify-content-md-center"},[n("b-col",{staticClass:"text-left",attrs:{cols:"6"}},[e.show?n("b-form",{on:{submit:e.addNewCard}},[n("b-form-group",{attrs:{id:"input-group-1",label:"Existing Categories:","label-for":"input-1"}},[n("b-form-select",{attrs:{id:"input-1",options:e.categoryNames,required:""},model:{value:e.selectCategory,callback:function(t){e.selectCategory=t},expression:"selectCategory"}})],1),"Create New Category"==e.selectCategory?n("div",[n("b-form-group",{attrs:{id:"newCat-group-1",label:"Name of new Category:","label-for":"newCat-1"}},[n("b-form-input",{attrs:{id:"newCat-1",placeholder:"Ex. The name of my new category"},model:{value:e.form.name,callback:function(t){e.$set(e.form,"name",t)},expression:"form.name"}})],1),n("b-form-group",{attrs:{id:"newCat-group-2",label:"Category Description:","label-for":"newCat-2"}},[n("b-form-input",{attrs:{id:"newCat-2",placeholder:'Ex. Flashcards in the "   " category'},model:{value:e.form.description,callback:function(t){e.$set(e.form,"description",t)},expression:"form.description"}})],1),n("b-form-group",{attrs:{id:"newCat-group-3",label:"Category Difficulty:","label-for":"newCat-3"}},[n("b-form-input",{attrs:{id:"newCat-3",placeholder:"Ex. 3"},model:{value:e.form.difficulty,callback:function(t){e.$set(e.form,"difficulty",t)},expression:"form.difficulty"}})],1)],1):e._e(),e.selectCategory?n("div",[n("b-form-group",{attrs:{id:"input-group-2",label:"Flashcard Question:","label-for":"input-2"}},[n("b-form-input",{attrs:{id:"input-2",required:"",placeholder:"Ex. How much wood could a wood chuck chuck?"},model:{value:e.question,callback:function(t){e.question=t},expression:"question"}})],1),n("b-form-group",{attrs:{id:"input-group-3",label:"Flashcard Answer:","label-for":"input-3"}},[n("b-form-input",{attrs:{id:"input-3",required:"",placeholder:"Ex. 21 parcels"},model:{value:e.answer,callback:function(t){e.answer=t},expression:"answer"}})],1),n("b-button",{attrs:{type:"submit",variant:"primary"},on:{click:function(t){return t.preventDefault(),e.addNewCard(t)}}},[e._v("Create card")])],1):e._e()],1):e._e(),e.message?n("show-alert",{attrs:{message:e.message}}):e._e()],1)],1)},D=[],P=(n("b0c0"),n("b64b"),n("ac1f"),n("5319"),function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,n=e._self._c||t;return n("div",[n("br"),n("b-alert",{attrs:{variant:"success",show:e.dismissCountDown,fade:""},on:{"dismiss-count-down":e.countDownChanged}},[e._v(e._s(e.message))])],1)}),N=[],F={props:["message"],data:function(){return{dismissSecs:2,dismissCountDown:0}},methods:{countDownChanged:function(e){this.dismissCountDown=e}},watch:{message:function(){this.dismissCountDown=this.dismissSecs}}},W=F,z=Object(c["a"])(W,P,N,!1,null,null,null),R=z.exports,H={mounted:function(){var e=this;E.all("categories").then((function(t){e.categories=t}))},components:{"show-alert":R},data:function(){return{categories:null,selectCategory:null,categoryName:"",question:"",answer:"",form:{name:"",description:"",difficulty:"",cards:[{answer:this.answer,question:this.question}],slug:this.categorySlug},show:!0,message:"",lastMessage:""}},methods:{addNewCard:function(){if("Create New Category"==this.selectCategory)E.add("categories",this.form).then((function(e){console.log("Category was added with the id: "+e)})),this.message="New Category and Card added!";else{var e={answer:this.answer,question:this.question};E.get_id_name("categories","name",this.selectCategory).then((function(t){E.addCard("categories",Object.values(t)[0],e)})),this.message="Card added to "+this.selectCategory}this.lastMessage==this.message&&(this.message=this.message+" "),this.lastMessage=this.message,this.answer="",this.question="",this.form={name:"",description:"",difficulty:"",cards:[{answer:this.answer,question:this.question}],slug:this.categorySlug}}},computed:{categoryNames:function(){if(this.categories){var e=[{text:"Select One",value:null}];e.push("Create New Category");for(var t=0,n=Object.keys(this.categories);t<n.length;t++){var a=n[t];e.push(this.categories[a].name)}return e}return[{text:"Loading...",value:null}]},categorySlug:function(){return this.form.name.replace(/\s+/g,"-").toLowerCase()}}},L=H,$=Object(c["a"])(L,M,D,!1,null,"4326c264",null),Q=$.exports,B=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,n=e._self._c||t;return e.category?n("b-container",{attrs:{id:"category-page"}},[n("b-row",{attrs:{"align-h":"end"}},[n("b-col",{attrs:{cols:"8"}},[n("h2",[e._v(e._s(e.category.name))]),n("div",{staticClass:"description"},[e._v(e._s(e.category.description))]),n("div",{staticClass:"difficulty"},[e._v(" Difficulty: "),n("b",[e._v(e._s(e.category.difficulty))])])]),n("b-col",{attrs:{cols:"2"}},[n("b-form-group",{staticClass:"text-right"},[n("b-form-radio-group",{attrs:{id:"radio-group-1",options:e.options,name:"radio-options",stacked:"",buttons:"","button-variant":"outline-primary"},model:{value:e.currentMode,callback:function(t){e.currentMode=t},expression:"currentMode"}})],1)],1)],1),e.currentCard&&"question"==e.currentSide?n("b-card",{staticClass:"mx-auto currentCard",staticStyle:{"min-width":"20rem","max-width":"200rem"},attrs:{title:"Question:",align:"left"}},[n("b-card-text",{staticClass:"currentCardText"},[e._v(e._s(e.currentCard.question))]),n("b-card-footer",{attrs:{"footer-bg-variant":"white"}},[n("b-row",{attrs:{"align-v":"center"}},["quiz"==e.currentMode?n("b-col",[e._v(" Answer: "),n("input",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model.trim",value:e.answerAttempt,expression:"answerAttempt",modifiers:{trim:!0}}],attrs:{type:"text"},domProps:{value:e.answerAttempt},on:{keydown:function(t){return!t.type.indexOf("key")&&e._k(t.keyCode,"enter",13,t.key,"Enter")?null:e.checkAnswer(t)},input:function(t){t.target.composing||(e.answerAttempt=t.target.value.trim())},blur:function(t){return e.$forceUpdate()}}}),n("b-button",{staticClass:"button",attrs:{variant:"outline-primary"},on:{click:e.checkAnswer}},[e._v("Submit")])],1):n("b-col",[n("b-button",{staticClass:"button",attrs:{variant:"outline-primary"},on:{click:e.randomCard}},[e._v("Next Question")])],1),n("b-col",{staticClass:"text-right"},[n("b-button",{staticClass:"button",attrs:{variant:"outline-primary"},on:{click:e.seeAnswer}},[e._v("See Answer")])],1)],1)],1)],1):e._e(),e.currentCard&&"answer"==e.currentSide?n("b-card",{staticClass:"mx-auto currentCard",staticStyle:{"min-width":"20rem","max-width":"200rem"},attrs:{title:"Answer:",align:"left"}},[n("b-card-text",{staticClass:"currentCardText"},[e._v(e._s(e.currentCard.answer))]),n("b-card-footer",{attrs:{"footer-bg-variant":"white"}},[n("b-row",[n("b-col",[n("b-button",{staticClass:"button",attrs:{variant:"outline-primary"},on:{click:e.randomCard}},[e._v("Next Question")])],1),"study"==e.currentMode?n("b-col",{staticClass:"text-right"},[n("b-button",{staticClass:"button",attrs:{variant:"outline-primary"},on:{click:e.seeAnswer}},[e._v("See Question")])],1):e._e()],1)],1)],1):e._e(),"correct!"==e.status?n("b-alert",{attrs:{show:e.dismissCountDown,fade:"",variant:"success"},on:{"dismiss-count-down":e.countDownChanged}},[e._v("Success Correct 100% Wow! Superb")]):"incorrect"==e.status?n("b-alert",{attrs:{show:e.dismissCountDown,fade:"",variant:"danger"},on:{"dismiss-count-down":e.countDownChanged}},[e._v("Incorrect, try again!")]):e._e()],1):e._e()},K=[],G={props:["slug"],data:function(){return{category:[],currentCard:null,currentSide:"question",currentMode:"quiz",answerAttempt:"",status:"guessing",dismissSecs:2,dismissCountDown:0,lastWord:null,options:[{text:"Quiz Mode",value:"quiz"},{text:"Study Mode",value:"study"}]}},mounted:function(){var e=this;E.get_slug("categories",this.slug).then((function(t){e.category=t,e.randomCard()}))},methods:{randomCard:function(){if(1==this.category.cards.length)this.currentCard=this.category.cards[0];else if(null==this.currentCard)this.currentCard=this.category.cards[Math.floor(Math.random()*this.category.cards.length+1)];else while(this.currentCard.question===this.lastWord)this.currentCard=this.category.cards[Math.floor(Math.random()*this.category.cards.length+1)];this.lastWord=this.currentCard.question,this.currentSide="question"},checkAnswer:function(){this.answerAttempt.toLowerCase()===this.currentCard.answer.toLowerCase()?(this.status="correct!",this.showAlert(),this.randomCard()):(this.status="incorrect",this.showAlert()),this.answerAttempt=""},seeAnswer:function(){"question"==this.currentSide?this.currentSide="answer":(this.currentSide="question","quiz"==this.category.type&&this.randomCard())},countDownChanged:function(e){this.dismissCountDown=e},showAlert:function(){this.dismissCountDown=this.dismissSecs}}},U=G,V=Object(c["a"])(U,B,K,!1,null,"08f26bff",null),X=V.exports,J=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,n=e._self._c||t;return n("div",[n("h2",[e._v("Admin")]),n("em",[e._v(" Disclaimer: This functionality is for demonstration purposes only. In a real-world application, this functionality must be locked down to administrators only. ")]),n("button",{on:{click:e.clearApi}},[e._v("Clear API")]),n("button",{on:{click:e.seedApi}},[e._v("Seed API")]),e.message?n("div",{staticClass:"alert"},[e._v(e._s(e.message))]):e._e()])},Z=[],Y=[{slug:"political_science-flashcards",name:"Political Science Flashcards",description:"Questions related to Political Science",difficulty:4,cards:[{question:"How did colonized peoples struggle against Europeans?",answer:"Between the 1870s and 1900, Africa faced European imperialist aggression, diplomatic pressures, military invasions, and eventual conquest and colonization. At the same time, African societies put up various forms of resistance against the attempt to colonize their countries and impose foreign domination."},{question:"How did Europeans imperialize and colonize Africa and Asia?",answer:"Between the 1870s and 1900, Africa faced European imperialist aggression, diplomatic pressures, military invasions, and eventual conquest and colonization. At the same time, African societies put up various forms of resistance against the attempt to colonize their countries and impose foreign domination."},{question:"How did Imperialism help lead to and cause a global World War?",answer:"The war started mainly because of four aspects: Militarism, Alliances, Imperialism and Nationalism. This is because big armies become potential threats to other countries, other countries started forcing alliances in order to secure land. ... The overall cause of World War was the assassination of Archduke Franz Ferdinand."},{question:"How did industrialization in Europe lead to imperialism and colonialism in Africa and Asia?",answer:"Africa that made the administration of colonial holdings much more efficient. ... Africa and Asia much more important to the industrial powers of Europe"},{question:"What is Imperialism?",answer:"a policy of extending a country's power and influence through diplomacy or military force."},{question:"What is nationalism and what role did it play in the Age of Imperialism?",answer:"an extreme form of this, especially marked by a feeling of superiority over other countries."},{question:"What is Social Darwinism and what role did it play in the Age of Imperialism?",answer:"the theory that individuals, groups, and peoples are subject to the same Darwinian laws of natural selection as plants and animals.Social Darwinism was a sociological theory popular in late nineteenth-century Europe and the United States. It merged Charles Darwin's theory of natural selection and Herbert Spencer's sociological theories to justify imperialism, racism, and laissez-faire (i.e. conservative) social and economic policies."},{question:"Where did European imperialism chiefly take place?",answer:"European states established vast empires mainly in Africa, but also in Asia and the Middle East"},{question:"Why did enlightened Europeans accept Imperial rule over Africans and Asians?",answer:"European nations sought trade ... This New Imperialist Age gained its impetus from economic, military, political, ... and was helpful in convincing Africans and Asians to accept Western control. .... the rebellion, the British government made India part of the empire in 1858, ..."}]},{slug:"learn_spanish-flashcards",name:"Spanish Flashcards",description:"Spanish to English Flashcards",difficulty:2,cards:[{question:"el concierto",answer:"The concert"},{question:"el partido",answer:"Game,match"},{question:"fiesta de cumpleaÃ±os",answer:"a birthday party"},{question:"la casa de mi amigo",answer:"my friend's house"},{question:"mi casa",answer:"my house"},{question:"el estadio",answer:"the stadium"},{question:"el centro commercial",answer:"shopping center"}]},{slug:"learn_nutrition-flashcards",name:"Nutrition Flashcards",description:"Nutrition terms and definitions Flashcards",difficulty:2,cards:[{answer:"appetite",question:"the want for food"},{answer:"calorie",question:"a unit of heat used to measure the energy of your body uses"},{answer:"carbohydrates",question:"starches and sugars that provide the bodies main energy"},{answer:"cholesterol",question:"a waxy fatlike substance"},{answer:"fiber",question:"a tough complex carb the body cannot digest"},{answer:"hunger",question:"the natural desire for food"},{answer:"minerals",question:"elements found in food that are used for the body"},{answer:"nutrients",question:"substances in your food your body needs to grow, heal, and get energy"},{answer:"nutrition",question:"the process of your body taking and using food"},{answer:"osteoporosis",question:"\ta condition where bones become weak an break easily"},{answer:"proteins",question:"nutrients the body uses to maintain its cell tissues"},{answer:"vitamins",question:"compounds found in food that help regulate body processes"}]},{slug:"learn_parts_of_body-flashcards",name:"Anatomy Flashcards",description:"Anatomy terms and definitions Flashcards",difficulty:5,cards:[{answer:"Amygdala",question:"The Amygdala is associated with the emotions of fear and anger; playing a key role in our emotional responses"},{answer:"Brain stem",question:"Connection to spinal cord. Filters information flow between peripheral nervous system and the rest of the brain."},{answer:"Central Nervous System (CNS)",question:"consists of the brain and spinal cord"},{answer:"Cerebellum",question:"Primitive part of the brain responsible for coordination, balance and movement"},{answer:"Cerebral cortex",question:"Most visible part of the brain responsible for conscious thought (made up of billions of nerve cells called neurons)"},{answer:"Cerebrospinal fluid",question:"Fluid in the space between the meninges that acts as a shock absorber that protects the central nervous system."},{answer:"Controlled variable",question:"Is always held constant during an experiment"},{answer:"Corpus Callosum",question:"This area contains the largest bundle of nerve fibers in the brain and connects both hemispheres (left and right)"},{answer:"Cranium",question:"the part of the skull that encloses the brain (the skull)"},{answer:"CT scan",question:"Can detect brain tissue abnormalities, specialised type of X-ray that highlights different parts within the brain"},{answer:"Dependant variable",question:"The outcome factor; the variable that may change in response to manipulations of the independent variable."},{answer:"EEG",question:"An electroencephalogram is a test designed to evaluate the electrical activity in the brain."},{answer:"Ethical Guidelines",question:"Ethical guidelines must be followed and experiments must be submitted and approved by an ethics committee before they can be undertaken. These include; No lasting harm to the participant, informed consent, confidentiality, voluntary participation, right to withdraw, minimal deception and debriefing"},{answer:"fMRI",question:"fMRI, or (Functional Magnetic resonance imaging) measures brain activity by detecting changes associated with blood flow. It associates the parts of the brain involved in specific functions used to indicate both normal and abnormal structures & functions."},{answer:"Frontal lobe",question:"Largest lobe of the brain, located at the front of both left and right hemispheres. Associated with thinking, decision making, personality, emotional behaviour, speech, self awareness, planning voluntary muscle movements and the judging of consequences"},{answer:"Hippocampus",question:"Responsible for making new memories; is also our navigator and helps us get around"},{answer:"Hypothalamus",question:"A neural structure lying below the thalamus; it directs several maintenance activities (eating, drinking, body temperature), helps govern the endocrine system via the pituitary gland, and is linked to emotion and reward."},{answer:"Hypothesis",question:"A hypothesis is the idea or explanation that you can test through study and experimentation. It is a prediction of what you expect to occur in a study."},{answer:"Independent Variable (IV)",question:"The experimental factor that is manipulated; the variable whose effect is being studied."},{answer:"Left Hemisphere",question:"The left side of the brain that controls the right side of the body"},{answer:"MRI",question:"Used for creating a clear and specific image of different regions of the brain; can distinguish between normal and abnormal brain tissues"},{answer:"Neglect syndrome",question:"-damage to right parietal lobe disrupts attention to the left side of visual space in reality and memory"},{answer:"Neuropsychology",question:"Neuropsychology is the study of how thinking and behaviour are affected by brain disfunction. (The relationship between behaviour, emotion, and cognition on the one hand, and brain function of the other)"},{answer:"Occipital lobe",question:"A region of the cerebral cortex that processes visual information"},{answer:"Parietal lobe",question:"A region of the cerebral cortex whose functions include taking in information about touch."},{answer:"Peripheral Nervous System",question:"The nervous system outside the CNS (Spinal cord & brain)"},{answer:"PET",question:"Indicates areas of the brain while performing taks. Shows bloodflow, rate of oxygen etc"},{answer:"Pineal gland",question:"a small endocrine gland in the brain; secretes melatonin."},{answer:"Pseudoscience",question:"Pseudoscience is a fake science that makes claims on non existent scientific evidence. Examples of Pseudoscience's include; Astrology, Phrenology and Extrasensory perception (ESP)"},{answer:"Right hemisphere",question:"controls the left side of the body; creative, intuitive, spacial"},{answer:"Temporal lobe",question:"One of the main four lobes of the cerebral cortex. This part of the cerebrum helps us with speech and hearing and learning language"},{answer:"Thalamus",question:"Sensory data arrives here and is then relaying sensory information and acting as a centre for pain perception."}]},{slug:"geometry-flashcards",name:"Geometry Flashcards",description:"Questions related to Geometry",difficulty:1,cards:[{answer:"acute triangle",question:"A triangle with 3 acute angles"},{answer:"Area",question:"The number of square units required to cover a surface."},{answer:"Base angles",question:"Two angles that have the base as a side."},{answer:"base angles of an isosceles triangle",question:"the angles opposite the legs of an isosceles triangle."},{answer:"Base of an isosceles triangle",question:"the non-congruent side of an isosceles triangle"},{answer:"Base of an isosceles triangle",question:"the side opposite the vertex angle"},{answer:"Circumference",question:"The distance around a circle"},{answer:"equiangular triangle",question:"A triangle with 3 congruent angles"},{answer:"Equilateral triangle",question:"A triangle with three congruent sides"},{answer:"Exterior angle of a triangle",question:"equals sum of opposite interior angles"},{answer:"Hinge Theorem",question:"If two sides of one triangle are congruent to two sides of another triangle, and the included angle of the first is larger than the included angle of the second, then the third side of the first is longer than the third side of the second."},{answer:"Hinge Theorem Converse",question:"If 2 sides of one triangle are congruent to two sides of another triangle, and the third side of the first is longer than the third side of the second, then the included angle of the first is larger than the included angle of the second."},{answer:"Hypotenuse",question:"the longest side of a right triangle"},{answer:"Hypotenuse (of a right triangle)",question:"the side opposite the right angle"},{answer:"Interior angle of a triangle",question:"an angle on the inside of a triangle. The sides of the angle are sides of the triangle."},{answer:"Isosceles triangle",question:"a triangle with at least two congruent sides"},{answer:"Isosceles Triangle Theorem Converse",question:"If 2 angles of a triangle are congruent, then the sides opposite those angles are congruent."},{answer:"Legs of an isosceles triangle",question:"the two congruent sides of an isosceles triangle"},{answer:"Legs of a right triangle",question:"the two sides that form the right angle"},{answer:"Linear units",question:"unit used to measure length"},{answer:"Midpoint",question:"A point that divides a segment into two congruent segments"},{answer:"Midsegment",question:"a segment that joins the midpoints of two sides of the triangle"},{answer:"Midsegment Theorem",question:"The segment connecting the midpoints of two sides of a triangle is parallel to the third side and is half as long as that side."},{answer:"Midsegment Triangle",question:"segment that connects the midpoints of two sides of a triangle"},{answer:"Obtuse Triangle",question:"A triangle with one angle that is greater than 90 degrees."},{answer:"obtuse triangle",question:"a triangle with one obtuse angle"},{answer:"Perimeter",question:"The distance around a figure"},{answer:"Perpendicular bisector",question:"A line that is perpendicular to a segment at its midpoint."},{answer:"Pi",question:"The ratio of the circumference of a circle to its diameter /3.14/"},{answer:"right triangle",question:"a triangle with one right angle"},{answer:"scalene triangle",question:"a triangle with no congruent sides"},{answer:"Sides",question:"The segments of a triangle"},{answer:"Square units",question:"a unit used in measuring area"},{answer:"triangle",question:"A polygon with three sides."},{answer:"Triangle Inequality Theorem",question:"The sum of the lengths of any two sides of a triangle is greater than the length of the third side."},{answer:"vertex",question:"A point where two or more straight lines meet."},{answer:"Vertex angle",question:"The angle formed by the legs of an isosceles triangle."}]}],ee={name:"",data:function(){return{message:"",collections:{categories:Y}}},methods:{clearApi:function(){var e=function(e){E.all(e).then((function(t){Object.keys(t).forEach((function(t){E.delete(e,t)}))}))};for(var t in this.collections)e(t);this.message="Clearing API"},seedApi:function(){for(var e in this.collections)for(var t in this.collections[e])E.add(e,this.collections[e][t]);this.message="Seeding API"}}},te=ee,ne=(n("ff2b"),Object(c["a"])(te,J,Z,!1,null,"37cf8f0c",null)),ae=ne.exports;a["default"].use(d["a"]),a["default"].use(h["a"]),a["default"].use(f["a"]),a["default"].config.productionTip=!1;var re=[{path:"/",component:O,name:"home"},{path:"/create",component:Q,name:"create"},{path:"/category/:slug",component:X,name:"category",props:!0},{path:"/admin",component:ae}],ie=new d["a"]({routes:re,mode:"history"});new a["default"]({router:ie,render:function(e){return e(l)}}).$mount("#app")},"5c0b":function(e,t,n){"use strict";var a=n("9c0c"),r=n.n(a);r.a},"9c0c":function(e,t,n){},ff2b:function(e,t,n){"use strict";var a=n("2fb8"),r=n.n(a);r.a}});
//# sourceMappingURL=app.07fe9159.js.map